whenever he goes this long without food
makes forced to Turin to a unlikely
place
all I want is eased he said in
for the Rome best price I know
have a guaranteed a cue or maybe an
entire meal
is a roadkill on the highways are here
constantly kill an elk near
anything and dryers across a just off
Highway 101
mix obeying roadkill isn't far
years goner rune gonna be doing some
running
group ish turn it comes a car combat
on
see what I got rumored to get out here
to go after and sex is certain to get
hit by cars
mix eating roadkill many times before
but this mountain chickadee has only in
out some meat spewed a forum luckily
he has another planned for the bird now
I can use this is made
Anna catch some nigger another Carlos
get back in the woods
three miles from here on is the closest
structure Pacific shoreline
so make kids for the water bobbing his
birdie
can land democrat gym
are you a little guy
yes I gotta the feather
now openers from me were give up the
good old
college try Amana Colonies
so
will morsel floating around well let's
give it a try and see what happens
now makes ready to start grabbing
so we heads for a title work calm water
will help ease of